emailquestions.com 2014-01-25

# Email Questions Privacy Policy Statement

    Hello,
    
    Welcome to the [Email Questions](http://www.emailquestons.com/) Privacy Policy Page.
    
    The privacy of our visitors to EmailQuestions.com is important to us. 
    
    At EmailQuestions.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is
    important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive
    and collect when you use visit EmailQuestions.com, and how we safeguard your 
    information.  We never sell your personal information to third parties.
    
    Log Files
    
    As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files.
    The information in the log files include  your IP (internet protocol) address, 
    your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser 
    you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you
    visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. 
    
    Cookies and Web Beacons
    
    We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when 
    you visit our site.  This could include only showing you a popup once in your 
    visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.
    
    We also use third party advertisements on EmailQuestions.com to support our site.  
    Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons 
    when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such 
    as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP 
    address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, 
    whether you have Flash installed.  This is generally used for geotargeting 
    purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example)
    or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking
     ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).
    
        * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.
        * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.
        * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. 
    
    You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party 
    cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such 
    as [Norton Internet Security](http://www.emailquestions.com/out.php?q=norton).  However, this can affect how you are able to 
    interact with our site as well as other websites.  This could include the 
    inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or 
    accounts.
    
    EmailQuestions.com collects the e-mail addresses of those who make postings to our
    forums and information volunteered by members in their member profile.
    
    The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web
    page, used to customize the content and/or layout of our page for
    each individual visitor, and used to notify members about updates to the site.
    
    If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please
    let us know by updating your options using your control panel by visiting us 
    at http://www.emailquestions.com/usercp.php.
    
    With respect to security: When we transfer and receive certain types
    of sensitive information such as a paypal donation, we redirect visitors 
    to a secure server and will notify visitors through a secure web page.
    
    Thank you,
    EmailQuestions.com
